superwebtricks.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy and Terms | Showeblogin

## Welcome to the Showeblogin Privacy Policy and Terms of Service

**Showeblogin Privacy Policy**

SuperWebTricks.com knows that you care how information about you is collected, used and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. We are committed to protecting your information and respecting your privacy rights. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it.

We collect information like name and email address from you while you sign up for our Email Newsletter, subscribe the RSS Feed and register yourself for any quiz contests on our website or submitting any forms or giving your opinion through commenting on our site. Moreover, we are using Google Analytics to see you live and to collect your location, browser data and device information etc.

The collected information may be used to communicate with you and provide better personalized services and user experience. Your information is fully secure with us and we never either share or sell your any data to anyone in any manner.

However, we are using [Google AdSense](http://www.superwebtricks.com/earn-money-online/adsense-approval-for-blog-website/), [Affiliate Ads](http://www.superwebtricks.com/earn-money-online/alternate-contents-affiliate-ads-for-adblock/) and [Direct advertisements](http://www.superwebtricks.com/advertise/) and therefore your web browser automatically sends certain information to them. You may read in details that [how Google uses your data](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) when you visit our site. Showing ads helps us offer many of our services for free to our users and live visitors.

Hence, we use cookies to personalise content and advertisements, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.

**Showeblogin Terms of Service**

Thanks for visiting our site and using our services. We are here to provide our users free as well as premium services and tutorial guidelines for informative purpose. So, please don’t misuse our website contents and services.

**Copyright Policy:** If you are interested in quoting, linking or printing any article or tutorial guide from Showeblogin in whole or in part, you are responsible to abide our copyright policy:

You are free to use short quotes (summary or excerpts) of any posts published on Showeblogin provided the proper credit has been given to the source webpage.

Thus, you have to provide a hyperlink (full URL) to the source post from where you have copied the extracts. Provided that you are not allowed use techniques (like rel=nofollow) that try to hide credits from search engines.  
The best practice is to enclose the copied contents within quotation marks and mention Showeblogin immediately before or after the quote along with hyperlink.

You may however not allowed copy paste whole contents of Showeblogin i.e. you should never republish our tutorials in any manner without written permission.

**Comments:** We keep all the rights to accept or reject your opinions provided through comments. We love comments but we have zero tolerance to spam. Each and every comments on our site is manually reviewed. Any comment which is abusive or hurting anyone in any manner will never be entertained. Further, the comments which contain any link(s) will either be deleted immediately or appears only after review and approval.

**Disclaimers:** This website is meant for educational, guidance and learning purposes since 1st of January 2014. Thus, the contents of this site are informatory in nature. While every efforts has been taken to provide all tutorials in a very descriptive way and to avoid errors, the owners and Authors are not responsible for the consequences of any action taken on the basis of the contents/ links provided in this site.

We have taken all reasonable care to ensure that the contents of the site do not violate any existing copyright of any person in any manner whatsoever. In the event we have unable to track any source and if any copyright has been inadvertently infringed, please [notify us](http://www.superwebtricks.com/contact/) for corrective action.

**Third party websites:** This website may contain hyperlinks to websites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the content of such websites, or the manner in which those websites collect, store, use, and distribute any personal information you provide. When you visit third party websites from hyperlinks displayed on this website, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of those websites so that you can understand how the personal information you provide may be collected, stored, used and distributed.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy and Terms of services:** We reserve the right to change these privacy policies, Terms of services from time to time by publishing the revised one on our website.

_Last modified: August 27, 2015_
